// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Cube root of 1331 is:",
    answer: "11",
    options: ["11", "13", "12", "17"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The value of pi is equal to:",
    answer: "22/7",
    options: ["24/7", "22/7", "23/7", "22/8"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the most sensitive organ in our body?",
    answer: "Skin",
    options: ["Skin", "Heart", "Brain", "Stomach"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The circumference of the circle is also sometimes called:",
    answer: "Perimeter of a circle",
    options: [
      "Arc of a circle",
      "Area of a circle",
      "Perimeter of a circle",
      "Diameter of a circle",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who invented Computer?",
    answer: "Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "Bill Gates",
      "Charles Babbage",
      "Alexander Cumming",
      "Mark Zuckerberg",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The area of rectangle is equal to:",
    answer: "Length x Breadth",
    options: [
      "Length x Breadth",
      "2 x (Length x Breadth)",
      "2 x (Length - Breadth)",
      "Â½ x base x height ",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The square root of 5 is",
    answer: "2.23",
    options: ["2.24", "2.23", "2.50", "2.89"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is known as Father of Indian Constitution? ",
    answer: "Dr. B. R. Ambedkar",
    options: [
      "Mahatama Gandhi",
      "Jawaharlal Nehru",
      "Dr. B. R. Ambedkar",
      "Subash Chandra Bose",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "1024 Kilobytes is equal to?",
    answer: "1 MB",
    options: ["10 MB", "1 TB", "1 MB", "1 GB"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "8 raised to power 0 is:",
    answer: "1",
    options: ["1", "0", "8", "Undefined"],
  },
];
